Guide to the John Vliet Lindsay Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- New York City Mayoral Personal Papers, 1965-1973; Part II
  - Speech Files, 1966-1969; Series V
    - The German Society of New York, 1969 March 29 (Box 83, Folder 846)
    - Anti-Defamation League, 1969 March 31 (Box 83, Folder 847)
    - The Association of the Bar of the City of New York, 1969 April 7 (Box 83, Folder 848)
    - Mets Welcome Home Dinner, 1969 April 7 (Box 83, Folder 849)
    - New York Convention and Visitors Bureau, Inc., 1969 April 8 (Box 83, Folder 850)
    - Opening of Lindsay - Garelik - Perrotta Campaign Headquarters at 38th St., and Madison, 1969 April 8 (Box 83, Folder 851)
    - The American Arbitration Association, 1969 April 9 (Box 83, Folder 852)
    - The American Museum of Natural History, 1969 April 9 (Box 83, Folder 853)
    - Motion Picture Association of America, Inc., 1969 April 10 (Box 83, Folder 854)
    - City of New York Pan American Week Luncheon, 1969 April 11 (Box 83, Folder 855)
    - Young Republican Dinner, 1969 April 11 (Box 83, Folder 856)
    - "Direct Line" appearance, 1969 April 11 (Box 83, Folder 857)
    - Pelham Parkway playground, groundbreaking, 1969 April 12 (Box 83, Folder 858)
    - Manhattan West Republican Club, 1969 April 12 (Box 83, Folder 859)
    - Motion Picture Association of America, 1969 April 12 (Box 83, Folder 860)
    - Committee of 100 to Honor Judge William H. Booth, 1969 April 13 (Box 83, Folder 861)
    - Holy Name Society, 1969 April 13 (Box 83, Folder 862)
    - Welcome Home Lunch for New York Yankees, 1969 April 14 (Box 83, Folder 863)
    - Real Estate Board of the Bronx, 1969 April 14 (Box 83, Folder 864)
    - New York Building Congress, Inc., 1969 April 15 (Box 83, Folder 865)
    - Real Estate Advisory Commission of the Real Estate Department of New York, 1969 April 17 (Box 83, Folder 866)
    - The Bronx Board of Trade and Chamber of Commerce, 1969 April 17 (Box 83, Folder 867)
    - Citizens Budget Commission, 1969 April 17 (Box 83, Folder 868)
    - Park Republican Club, 1969 April 19 (Box 83, Folder 869)
    - Mt. Sinai School of Medicine, 1969 April 20 (Box 83, Folder 870)
    - Peninsula General Hospital, 1969 April 20 (Box 83, Folder 871)
    - Luis Munoz Rivera Community Improvement Association, Inc., dinner honoring Sid Davidoff, 1969 April 20 (Box 84, Folder 872)
    - Fashion Institute of Technology, 1969 April 21 (Box 84, Folder 873)
    - The Actors' Fund, 1969 April 21 (Box 84, Folder 874)
    - New York City Housing Authority, Tenants Awards, 1969 April 22 (Box 84, Folder 875)
    - Brimberg and Company, luncheon in honor of JVL, 1969 April 23 (Box 84, Folder 876)
    - Catholic Interracial Council of New York, 1969 April 23 (Box 84, Folder 877)
    - National Conference of Christian and Jews, dinner for Irving Felt, 1969 April 24 (Box 84, Folder 878)
    - Riverdale Community Council, dinner honoring Robert Rosenberg, 1969 April 24 (Box 84, Folder 879)
    - Queens County Republican Committee, 1969 April 24 (Box 84, Folder 880)
    - St. John's University, Annual Law Day, 1969 April 25 (Box 84, Folder 881)
    - Twenty-second Annual Loyalty Day Parade, 1969 April 26 (Box 84, Folder 882)
    - "Parents Night", Youth Week, 1969 April 28 (Box 84, Folder 883)
    - Eastside Young Republican Club, 1969 April 29 (Box 84, Folder 884)
    - City Athletic Club, 1969 April 29 (Box 84, Folder 885)
    - Veterans of Foreign Wars, Ridgewood Post No. 123, 1969 April 30 (Box 84, Folder 886)
    - Church Women United in Manhattan, 1969 May 2 (Box 84, Folder 887)
    - St. George Association, Inc., 1969 May 4 (Box 84, Folder 888)
    - Robert E. Lee Memorial Foundation, Inc., 1969 May 4 (Box 84, Folder 889)
    - New York City Transit Authority, 1969 May 6 (Box 84, Folder 890)
    - Lindsay - Hal Prince, 1969 May 11 (Box 84, Folder 891)
    - Out-of-town investors, 1969 May 14 (Box 84, Folder 892)
    - Newspaper Reporters Association installation, 1969 May 14 (Box 84, Folder 893)
    - Kiwanis Club of Bensonhurst and Bay Ridge, 1969 May 15 (Box 84, Folder 894)
    - Fordham University, Losenstein Center, dedication, 1969 May 15 (Box 84, Folder 895)
    - Investors luncheon, 1969 May 16 (Box 84, Folder 896)
    - Joint meeting of two Republican Clubs, 1969 May 16 (Box 84, Folder 897)
    - Joint meeting of two Republican Clubs, 1969 May 17 (Box 84, Folder 898)
    - The Laguardia Club, 1969 May 18 (Box 84, Folder 899)
    - The Association of Local Transit Airlines, 1969 May 18 (Box 84, Folder 900)
    - Housing Authority tour, 1969 May 19 (Box 84, Folder 901)
    - United Nations Association of New York, award ceremony for the annual high school contest (cancelled), 1969 May 19 (Box 84, Folder 902)
    - 1969 May 20 (Box 84, Folder 903)
    - "Salute to Queens", 1969 May 21 (Box 84, Folder 904)
    - 150th Anniversary of the New York Bank for Savings (cancelled), 1969 May 22 (Box 84, Folder 905)
    - Joint meeting of three Republican Clubs, 1969 May 22 (Box 84, Folder 906)
    - First S.D. Republican Ball, 1969 May 23 (Box 84, Folder 907)
    - Fund raising dinner for campaign - Lindsay Gala, 1969 May 25 (Box 84, Folder 908)
    - Second Annual Dr. Martin Luther King Memorial Parade, 1969 May 25 (Box 84, Folder 909)
    - Queens Captains Gathering, 1969 May 26 (Box 84, Folder 910)
    - Testimonial dinner for Fred Berman, 1969 May 27 (Box 84, Folder 911)
    - Joint meeting of three Brooklyn Republican Clubs, 1969 May 27 (Box 84, Folder 912)
    - Joint meeting of three Republican Clubs, 1969 May 28 (Box 84, Folder 913)
    - Sanitation Commission, promotion ceremonies, 1969 May 29 (Box 84, Folder 914)
    - Meeting of third Triennial Congress for Accident and Traffic Medicine, 1969 May 29 (Box 84, Folder 915)
    - Brooklyn Memorial Day Parade, 1969 May 30 (Box 84, Folder 916)
    - Manhattanville College, commencement, 1969 May 31 (Box 84, Folder 917)
    - Police Department, medal ceremonies, 1969 June 2 (Box 84, Folder 918)
    - Primary candidates meeting, 1969 June 2 (Box 84, Folder 919)
    - Fire Department, medal ceremonies, 1969 June 4 (Box 84, Folder 920)
    - New York Republican state Committee dinner, 1959 June 5 (Box 84, Folder 921)
    - Police Department, promotion ceremonies, 1969 June 5 (Box 84, Folder 922)
    - Dinner honoring Robert W. Sweet, 1969 June 6 (Box 84, Folder 923)
    - Holy Name Society of St. Ephram's church, 1969 June 12 (Box 84, Folder 924)
    - Our Lady of Peace for Cardinal Cooke, 1969 June 14 (Box 84, Folder 925)
  - Campaign Records, 1965; Series VI; 19 linear feet (47 boxes)
    Scope and Contents
    Series VI is sub-divided into the following sections:
    General Correspondence
    Issues Correspondence
    Position Papers
    Research Subject files
    Financial Records
    Campaign Literature and Memorabilia
    Schedules and Press Releases
    Biographical Newspaper Clippings
    - General Correspondence
      - A (Box 85, Folder 1)
      - B (Box 85, Folder 2)
      - C (Box 85, Folder 3)
      - D (Box 85, Folder 4)
      - E (Box 85, Folder 5)
      - F (Box 85, Folder 6)
      - G (Box 85, Folder 7)
      - H (Box 86, Folder 8)
      - I-J (Box 86, Folder 9)
      - K (Box 86, Folder 10)
      - L (Box 86, Folder 11)
      - M (Box 86, Folder 12)
      - N (Box 86, Folder 13-14)
      - O (Box 87, Folder 15)
      - P-Q (Box 87, Folder 16)
      - R (Box 87, Folder 17)
      - S (Box 87, Folder 18-19)
      - T (Box 87, Folder 20)
      - U-V (Box 87, Folder 21)
      - W (Box 87, Folder 22)
      - X-Y-Z (Box 87, Folder 23)
    - Issues Correspondence
      - Air pollution (Box 88, Folder 24)
      - Blackout (Box 88, Folder 25)
      - Buildings (Box 88, Folder 26)
      - City employees (Box 88, Folder 27)
      - Civil court (Box 88, Folder 28)
      - Civil defense (Box 88, Folder 29)
      - Congratulatory correspondence re: JVL's becoming Mayor (Box 88, Folder 30)
      - Consolidation of departments (Box 88, Folder 31)
      - Corrections, issues and background (Box 88, Folder 32)
      - Courts (Box 88, Folder 33)
      - Crime (Box 88, Folder 34)
      - Education (Box 88, Folder 35)
      - Election Board (Box 88, Folder 36)
      - Fire Commissioner Lowery (Box 88, Folder 37)
      - Fire Department (Box 88, Folder 38)
      - Fluoridation (Box 88, Folder 39)
      - Harren High School (Box 88, Folder 40)
      - Health Department (Box 88, Folder 41)
      - Highways (Box 88, Folder 42)
      - Hospital (Box 88, Folder 43)
      - Housing (Box 89, Folder 44-45)
      - Human Rights Commission (Box 89, Folder 46)
      - Labor (Box 89, Folder 47)
      - Licenses (Box 89, Folder 48)
      - Miscellaneous (unanswered correspondence) (Box 89, Folder 49)
      - Narcotics (Box 89, Folder 50)
      - Neighborhood Mayor's Office (Box 89, Folder 51)
      - New York State Racing Commission (Box 89, Folder 52)
      - Office of Mayor (Box 89, Folder 53)
      - Quill, Mike (Box 89, Folder 54)
      - Parks (Box 89, Folder 55)
      - Personnel (Box 89, Folder 56)
      - Plumbing industry (Box 89, Folder 57)
      - Police (Box 89, Folder 58)
      - Police Department Hack Bureau (Box 89, Folder 59)
      - Poverty (Box 89, Folder 60)
      - Public Administrative Office (Box 89, Folder 61)
      - Public Works Department (Box 89, Folder 62)
      - Purchase (Box 89, Folder 63)
      - Rent and rehabilitation (Box 89, Folder 64)
      - Rent control (Box 89, Folder 65)
      - Requests for employment (Box 90, Folder 66)
      - Sanitation (Box 90, Folder 67)
      - Shea Stadium dome (Box 90, Folder 68)
      - Taxes (Box 90, Folder 69)
      - Traffic (Box 90, Folder 70)
      - Transportation (Box 90, Folder 71)
      - Water supply, gas, electricity (Box 90, Folder 72)
      - Welfare (Box 90, Folder 73)
    - Position Papers
      - On problems and programs for the aging (Box 91, Folder 74)
      - Organization of the New York City government (Box 91, Folder 75)
      - Crime and safety "Operation Safe City" (Box 91, Folder 76)
      - Crime and law enforcement (Box 91, Folder 77)
      - Expanding the city's economy (Box 91, Folder 78)
      - Education in the city's schools (Box 91, Folder 79)
      - From fiscal decay to recovery (Box 91, Folder 80)
      - Crisis in hospital facilities and care, I (Box 91, Folder 81)
      - Crisis in hospital facilities and care, II (Box 91, Folder 82)
      - New Yorker's housing crisis: four year program (Box 91, Folder 83)
      - A program for housing code enforcement, attack on slums (Box 91, Folder 84)
      - Narcotics (Box 91, Folder 85)
      - Parks and recreation (Box 91, Folder 86)
      - A modern transportation system for New York City (Box 91, Folder 87)
    - Research Subject Files
      - Beame, Abe: campaign literature
        - General (Box 92, Folder 88)
        - Literature on Lindsay (Box 92, Folder 89)
        - Lindsay literature on Beame (Box 92, Folder 90)
        - Lindsay literature on Beame: "The Myth of Beame's Record" (Box 92, Folder 91)
      - Buckley, William F. Jr., campaign literature
        - Buckley position statements (Box 92, Folder 92)
        - Lindsay literature and newspaper clippings on Buckley (Box 92, Folder 93)
        - Clippings (Box 92, Folder 94-96)
        - Position statements: William F. Buckley Jr., Frank D. O' Conner, Mario A. Procaccino, William F. Ryan and Paul Screvane (Box 92, Folder 97)
      - Campaign technique, pamphlets (Box 93, Folder 98)
      - Coordinator's memoranda (Box 93, Folder 99)
      - Diamond, steve: campaign literature news release, "Speak up for Lindsay" (Box 93, Folder 100)
      - Ethnic, Irish (Box 93, Folder 101)
      - Fusion literature (Box 93, Folder 102)
      - Lindsay Awareness Study, 1965 August 11 (Box 93, Folder 103)
      - Lindsay John V.: "Personal and Political Quotes and Statements" (Box 93, Folder 104)
      - Marrow, Hugh: campaign literature
        - General information 1961 Mayoral Campaign (Box 93, Folder 105)
        - Opinion poll reports, 1961 Mayoral Campaign (Box 93, Folder 106)
      - Surveys, 1961 Mayoral Campaign (Box 93, Folder 107)
      - Neighborhood convassing (Box 94, Folder 108)
      - O'Conner, Frank: campaign literature, New York City Council President literature (Box 94, Folder 109)
      - O'Dwyer, Paul: campaign literature, candidate for Mayor, position papers (Box 94, Folder 110)
      - Procaccino, Mario A.: campaign literature, Beame - O'Conner - Procaccino press releases (Box 94, Folder 111-113)
      - Procaccino, Mario A.: campaign literature, Beame - O'Conner - Procaccino TV and press releases (Box 95, Folder 114-116)
      - Questionnaire (Box 95, Folder 117)
      - Ryan, William F.: campaign literature
        - Position papers, news releases, clippings (Box 95, Folder 118-120)
        - Position papers, news releases, clippings (Box 96, Folder 121)
        - Speech notes (Box 96, Folder 122)
        - Staff memoranda (Box 96, Folder 123)
        - Volunteers and election operations (Box 96, Folder 124)
      - Wagner, Robert F.
        - "The Administration of Robert F. Wagner," a summary (Box 96, Folder 125)
        - Position papers, news releases, clippings (Box 96, Folder 126)
        - Transit strike (Box 96, Folder 127)
    - Financial Records
      - Cancelled checks (Box 97, Folder 128-129)
      - Employees exemtion certificates, W-4's, 1T2104 N.Y. (Box 97, Folder 130)
      - Inter-office bulletins (Box 97, Folder 131)
      - Payroll routine, deposit slips, refund vouchers, Committee information (Box 97, Folder 132)
      - Petty cash journals (Box 97, Folder 133-135)
    - Campaign Literature and Memorabilia
      - Campaign Literature (Box 98, Folder 136)
        General note
        See also: box 438
      - Campaign literature (Box 98, Folder 137-142)
      - Campiagn literature, Hispanic community (Box 98, Folder 143)
      - Campaign memorabilia (Box 99, Folder 144-145)
      - Campaign memorabilia, invitations and cards (Box 99, Folder 146)
    - Schedules and Press Releases
      - Campaign indexes (Box 100, Folder 147)
      - Labor Day Weekend, 1965 September 3 (Box 100, Folder 148)
      - Dr. Costello's schedule, 1965 September 4-6 (Box 100, Folder 149)
      - Lindsay press office releases
        - 1965 September 4, 8-11, 13-14 1965 September 4, 8-11, 13-14 (Box 100, Folder 150-157)
      - Costello, Timothy
        - 1965 July 17-18, September 13, 15-20 1965 July 17-18, September 13, 15-20 (Box 100, Folder 158-167)
        - 1965 September 21-23, 28-30, October 2-3, 5-7, 9, 19-20, 22-25 1965 September 21-23, 28-30, October 2-3, 5-7, 9, 19-20, 22-25 (Box 100, Folder 168-186)
      - Abraham Beame
        - 1965 October 28 1965 October 28 (Box 100, Folder 187)
        - 1965 May 13-October 18 1965 May 13-October 18 (Box 101, Folder 188-190)
        - 1965 October 19-December 31 1965 October 19-December 31 (Box 102, Folder 191)
      - Air pollution (Box 103, Folder 192)
      - Amenities (Box 103, Folder 193)
      - Arts, theater, culture (Box 103, Folder 194)
      - Civil service - general (Box 103, Folder 195)
      - Courts, judges, crime, police narcotics (Box 103, Folder 196)
      - Economics, finance, taxes, including city and private industry (Box 103, Folder 197)
      - General campaign statements (Box 103, Folder 198)
      - General city planning (Box 103, Folder 199)
      - Hospitals, nursing, old age, medicare (Box 103, Folder 200)
      - Immigration, foreign issues (Box 103, Folder 201)
      - Immigration, civil rights, Harlem (Box 103, Folder 202)
      - Jobs, employment, unions, strikes (Box 103, Folder 203)
      - John V. Lindsay's record in Congress (Box 103, Folder 204)
      - Neighborhood issues (Box 103, Folder 205)
      - Non-meaty releases: photo capions, beer parties, etc. (Box 103, Folder 206)
      - Parks, beaches, recreation (Box 103, Folder 207)
      - Personnel, staff appointments (Box 103, Folder 208)
      - Registration and voting, general, Puerto Ricans (Box 103, Folder 209)
      - Rent, housing, urban development and renovation (Box 103, Folder 210)
      - Schools, education, headstart (Box 103, Folder 211)
      - Traffic and transit (Box 103, Folder 212)
      - Water, shortage, pollution (Box 103, Folder 213)
      - Youth, future, opportunity (Box 103, Folder 214)
      - Seymour Halpern, 1965 August 24 (Box 104, Folder 215)
      - Immigration bill, 1965 August 26 (Box 104, Folder 216)
      - Board of Estimate, park zoning, 1965 August 27 (Box 104, Folder 217)
      - Prospect Park, 1965 September 1 (Box 104, Folder 218)
      - Flushing Meadow Park, 1965 September 2 (Box 104, Folder 219)
      - New York Teachers, 1965 September 2 (Box 104, Folder 220)
      - Federal school aid, 1965 September 10 (Box 104, Folder 221)
      - Welfare Department, 1965 September 10 (Box 104, Folder 222)
      - City planning, 1965 September 17 (Box 104, Folder 223)
      - Democrats for Lindsay headquarters 49th street, 1965 September 23 (Box 104, Folder 224)
      - Promise two-hundred thousand jobs, 1965 September 23 (Box 104, Folder 225)
      - Michael McSherry Association, endorsement, 1965 September 24 (Box 104, Folder 226)
      - Obscenity (Smut), control, 1965 September 24 (Box 104, Folder 227)
      - Hospital budgets, 1965 September 27 (Box 104, Folder 228)
      - Beame and Firemen's Pension Fund, 1965 October 2 (Box 104, Folder 229)
      - Neighborhood Mayor's office, 1965 October 2 (Box 104, Folder 230)
      - Beame skimped on air pollution control, 1965 October 4 (Box 104, Folder 231)
      - Graft is rampant, 1965 October 6 (Box 104, Folder 232)
      - Concern for aged: health, safety, 1965 October 8 (Box 104, Folder 233)
      - New status for civil servants, 1965 October 8 (Box 104, Folder 234)
      - Citizens Union endorsement, 1965 October 9 (Box 104, Folder 235)
      - Beame ducks debates, 1965 October 11 (Box 104, Folder 236)
      - Inter-city cooperation planning, 1965 October 12 (Box 104, Folder 237)
      - End citizen apathy on crime, 1965 October 13 (Box 104, Folder 238)
      - JVL demands Beame debate, 1965 October 13 (Box 104, Folder 239)
      - Robert Price: Franklin Roosevelt Jr. using "hatchet tactics", 1965 October 13 (Box 104, Folder 240)
      - Javits Speech: JVL is progressive, 1965 October 14 (Box 104, Folder 241)
      - War on crime, 1965 October 16 (Box 104, Folder 242)
      - Crackdown on slumbids, 1965 October 18 (Box 104, Folder 243)
      - Modernize port of New York, 1965 October 18 (Box 104, Folder 244)
      - Action on problems of poor, 1965 October 19 (Box 104, Folder 245)
      - Beame opposed Wagner? Ha!, 1965 October 19 (Box 104, Folder 246)
      - Beame poverty plan illegal, 1965 October 21 (Box 104, Folder 247)
      - Javits Re: Radical Right, 1965 October 21 (Box 104, Folder 248)
      - "Operation Safe City," Crown Hieghts rally, 1965 October 21 (Box 104, Folder 249)
      - Welfare, Anti-Poverty Program, Port Authority Job Program (1965 Jun 25 - 1965 Oct 21), 1965 October 21 (Box 104, Folder 250)
      - Civil Rights, 1965 October 22 (Box 104, Folder 251)
      - Refute charges re: record, 1965 October 24 (Box 104, Folder 252)
      - Javits Re: Beame "arrogance" on Federal funds claim, 1965 October 25 (Box 104, Folder 253)
      - Javits Re: Beame using city machinery in campaign, 1965 October 25 (Box 104, Folder 254)
    - Biographical Newspaper Clippings
      - National
        - "Lindsay, a Man For Tomorrow (Box 105, Folder 255)
        - Newspaper and Magazine articles (Box 105, Folder 256-257)
        - Alabama (Box 106, Folder 258)
        - Alaska (Box 106, Folder 259)
        - Arkansas (Box 106, Folder 260)
        - Arizona, Phoenix (Box 106, Folder 261)
        - Arizona, Tuscon (Box 106, Folder 262)
        - California (Box 106, Folder 263)
        - California, Beverly Hills (Box 106, Folder 264)
        - California, Hollywood (Box 106, Folder 265)
        - California, Los Angeles (Box 106, Folder 266)
        - California, San Francisco (Box 106, Folder 267)
        - California, San Jose (Box 106, Folder 268)
        - Canada (Box 106, Folder 269)
        - Canada, Toronto (Box 106, Folder 270)
        - Colorado, Denver (Box 106, Folder 271)
        - Connecticut (Box 106, Folder 272)
        - Connecticut, Hartford (Box 106, Folder 273)
        - Connecticut, New Haven, including Yale publications (Box 106, Folder 274)
        - Delaware (Box 106, Folder 275)
        - Delaware, Dover (Box 106, Folder 276)
        - Delaware, Wilmington (Box 106, Folder 277)
        - England, London (Box 106, Folder 278)
        - Florida (Box 107, Folder 279)
        - Florida, Miami (Box 107, Folder 280)
        - Florida, St. Petersburg (Box 107, Folder 281)
        - France, Paris (Box 107, Folder 282)
        - Georgia, Atlanta (Box 107, Folder 283)
        - Hawaii, Honolulu (Box 107, Folder 284)
        - Idaho (Box 107, Folder 285)
        - Illinois (Box 107, Folder 286)
        - Illinois, Chicago (Box 107, Folder 287)
        - Illinois, Evanston (Box 107, Folder 288-289)
        - India, Lucknow (Box 107, Folder 290)
        - Indiana (Box 107, Folder 291)
        - Indiana, Indianapolis (Box 108, Folder 292)
        - Iowa (Box 108, Folder 293)
        - Iowa, Grand Rapids (Box 108, Folder 294)
        - Iowa, Des Moines (Box 108, Folder 295)
        - Israel (Box 108, Folder 296)
        - Italy (Box 108, Folder 297)
        - Kansas (Box 108, Folder 298)
        - Kansas, Leavenworth (Box 108, Folder 299)
        - Kentucky (Box 108, Folder 300)
        - Kentucky, Lexington (Box 108, Folder 301)
        - Kentucky, Louisville (Box 108, Folder 302)
        - Louisiana (Box 108, Folder 303)
        - Louisiana, New Orleans (Box 108, Folder 304)
        - Maine (Box 108, Folder 305)
        - Maryland (Box 108, Folder 306)
        - Maryland, Baltimore (Box 109, Folder 307)
        - Massachusetts (Box 109, Folder 308)
        - Massachusetts, Boston (Box 109, Folder 309)
        - Massachusetts, Pittsfield (Box 109, Folder 310)
        - Massachusetts, Springfield (Box 109, Folder 311)
        - Massachusetts, Worcester (Box 109, Folder 312)
        - Michigan (Box 109, Folder 313)
        - Michigan, Detroit (Box 109, Folder 314)
        - Minnesota (Box 109, Folder 315)
        - Minnesota, Duluth (Box 109, Folder 316)
        - Minnesota, Minneapolis (Box 109, Folder 317)
        - Minnesota, St. Paul (Box 110, Folder 318)
        - Missouri (Box 110, Folder 319)
        - Missouri, Kansas City (Box 110, Folder 320)
        - Missouri, St. Louis (Box 110, Folder 321)
        - Montana (Box 110, Folder 322)
        - Nebraska (Box 110, Folder 323)
        - Nevada (Box 110, Folder 324)
        - New Hampshire (Box 110, Folder 325)
        - New Hampshire, Concord (Box 110, Folder 326)
        - New Jersey (Box 110, Folder 327)
        - New Jersey, Asbury Park (Box 110, Folder 328)
        - New Jersey, Atlantic City (Box 110, Folder 329)
        - New Jersey, Bayonne (Box 110, Folder 330)
        - New Jersey, Camden (Box 110, Folder 331)
        - New Jersey, Elizabeth (Box 110, Folder 332)
        - New Jersey, Hackensack (Box 110, Folder 333)
        - New Jersey, Jersey City (Box 110, Folder 334)
        - New Jersey, Newark (Box 111, Folder 335-336)
        - New Jersey, New Brunswick (Box 111, Folder 337)
        - New Jersey, Passaic (Box 111, Folder 338)
        - New Jersey, Patterson (Box 111, Folder 339)
        - New Jersey, Perth Amboy (Box 111, Folder 340)
        - New Jersey, Plainfield (Box 111, Folder 341)
        - New Jersey, Trenton (Box 111, Folder 342)
        - New Jersey, Union City (Box 111, Folder 343)
        - North Carolina (Box 112, Folder 344-345)
        - North Carolina, Durham (Box 112, Folder 346)
        - North Carolina, Winston Salem (Box 112, Folder 347)
        - North Dakota (Box 112, Folder 348)